Preliminary Guide to the Joe Szabo Papers and Collection of Original Comic Art, 1960s-2000s SPEC.CGA.JGS
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Bratislava (Slovakia), 1991-1996 (Box JGS 21, Folder 5)
- Brazil, 1986-1991 (Box JGS 18, Folder 8)
- Bucuresti (Romania), 1993-1998 (Box JGS 21, Folder 6)
- Budapest, 1989-1993 (Box JGS 20, Folder 12-13)
- Bulgaria, 1987-1991 (Box JGS 18, Folder 9)
- Burma, 1993 (Box JGS 18, Folder 10)
- Calarca (Colombia), 1989-1990 (Box JGS 20, Folder 14)
- Canada, 1986-1994 (Box JGS 18, Folder 11)
- Centro (Mexico), 1996 (Box JGS 21, Folder 7)
- Chelya Binsk (USSR), 1992-1993 (Box JGS 21, Folder 8)
- China, 1986-1992 (Box JGS 18, Folder 12)
- Colombia, 1989 (Box JGS 18, Folder 13)
- Columbus (Ohio), 1995 (Box JGS 21, Folder 9)
- Costa Rica, undated (Box JGS 18, Folder 14)
- Cuba, 1988-1989 (Box JGS 18, Folder 15)
- Cuneo (Italy), 1991-1993 (Box JGS 20, Folder 15)
- Cyprus, 1989, 1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 16)
- Czechoslovakia, 1986-1994 (Box JGS 18, Folder 17)
- Denmark, 1986-1994 (Box JGS 18, Folder 18)
- East Germany, 1986 (Box JGS 18, Folder 19)
- Egypt, 1989 (Box JGS 18, Folder 20)
- England, 1986-1997 (Box JGS 18, Folder 21)
- Erlangen (Germany), 1988-1990 (Box JGS 20, Folder 16)
- Finland, 1992 (Box JGS 18, Folder 22)
- Foligno (Italy), 1990-2000 (Box JGS 20, Folder 17)
- Forte dei Marmi (Italy), 1988-1994 (Box JGS 20, Folder 17)
- France, 1985-1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 23)
- Greece, 1985-1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 24)
- Hamburg, 1989-2000 (Box JGS 20, Folder 18)
- Headliner (Atlantic City, New Jersey), 1993 (Box JGS 21, Folder 10)
- Holland, 1988-1989 (Box JGS 18, Folder 25)
- Homer (Silverton, Oregon), 1994-1996 (Box JGS 21, Folder 11)
- Hong Kong, 1986-1996 (Box JGS 18, Folder 26)
- Hungary, 1986-1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 27)
- Iceland, 1988 (Box JGS 18, Folder 28)
- India, 1985-1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 29)
- Indonesia, 1986-1988 (Box JGS 18, Folder 30)
- Iran, 1986-1998 (Box JGS 18, Folder 31)
- Iraq, 1986 (Box JGS 18, Folder 32)
- Ireland, 1985-1988 (Box JGS 18, Folder 33)
- Israel, 1984-1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 34)
- Italy, 1985-1993 (Box JGS 18, Folder 35)
- Japan, 1986-1996 (Box JGS 18, Folder 36)
- Jonzac Cedex (France), 1996 (Box JGS 20, Folder 19)
- Kagoshima (Japan), 1989-1996 (Box JGS 20, Folder 20)
- Kaliningrad (Russia), undated (Box JGS 21, Folder 12)
- Kallithea (Greece), undated (Box JGS 20, Folder 21)
- Kaposvar, 1993 (Box JGS 20, Folder 22)
- Kazan, 1990 (Box JGS 21, Folder 13)
- Kragujevac (Yugoslavia), 1981 (Box JGS 21, Folder 14)
- Krasnodar, undated (Box JGS 21, Folder 15)
- Korea, 1987-1996 (Box JGS 18, Folder 37)
- Kuwait, 1988 (Box JGS 18, Folder 38)
- Kyoto, 1989-1991 (Box JGS 20, Folder 23)
- Legnica (Poland), 1989-1996 (Box JGS 21, Folder 16)
- Lisbon (Portugal), 1994 (Box JGS 21, Folder 17)
- Longwood (Florida), 1994 (Box JGS 21, Folder 18)
- Los Angeles, 1996-1997 (Box JGS 21, Folder 19)
- Lucca (Italy), 1990-1992 (Box JGS 20, Folder 24)
- Marostica (Italy), 1994-1996 (Box JGS 20, Folder 25)
- Mexico, 1986-1993 (Box JGS 18, Folder 39)
- Miyagawa Village (Japan), 1994 (Box JGS 20, Folder 26)
- Mongolia, 1991 (Box JGS 18, Folder 40)
- Montevideo (Uruguay), 1990 (Box JGS 21, Folder 21)
- Moscow, 1991 (Box JGS 21, Folder 22)
- Nepal, 1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 41)
- The Netherlands, 1968-1991 (Box JGS 18, Folder 42)
- New York, 1994 (Box JGS 21, Folder 20)
- New Zealand, 1986-1991 (Box JGS 18, Folder 43)
- Nicaragua, 1986 (Box JGS 18, Folder 44)
- Nigeria, 1987-1989 (Box JGS 18, Folder 45)
- Norway, 1986-1992 (Box JGS 18, Folder 46)
- Odessa (Russia), 1988-2001 (Box JGS 21, Folder 23)
- Okhotsk (Japan), 1991 (Box JGS 20, Folder 27)
- Omiya (Japan), 1992-1994 (Box JGS 20, Folder 28)
- Overseas Press (NYC), 1996-1998 (Box JGS 21, Folder 24)
- Oviedo (Spain), 1987 (Box JGS 21, Folder 25)
- Peru, 1986 (Box JGS 18, Folder 47)
- Philippines, 1985-1988 (Box JGS 18, Folder 48)
- Pleasantville (New Jersey), 1997 (Box JGS 21, Folder 26)
- Podolsk (USSR), 1990 (Box JGS 21, Folder 27)
- Poland, 1985-1991 (Box JGS 18, Folder 49)
- San Diego, 1994 (Box JGS 21, Folder 28)
- Portugal, 1985-1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 50)
- Rathdrum (Ireland), 1993-1995 (Box JGS 20, Folder 29)
- Romania, 1987-1990 (Box JGS 18, Folder 51)
- St. Just le Martel (France), 1966-1994 (Box JGS 20, Folder 30)
- Semarang (Indonesia), 1988 (Box JGS 20, Folder 31)
- Siauliai (Lithuania), 1989-1991 (Box JGS 21, Folder 29)
- Silverton (Oregon), 1993-1996 (Box JGS 21, Folder 30)
- Sinaloa (Mexico), 1987-2000 (Box JGS 21, Folder 31)
- Singapore, 1990-1994 (Box JGS 18, Folder 52)
- Skopje (Macedonia), 1994 (Box JGS 21, Folder 32)
- Skopje (Yugoslavia), 1989-1991 (Box JGS 21, Folder 33)
- Slovakia, 1994-1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 53)
- Somerville (Massachusetts), 1994 (Box JGS 21, Folder 34)
- South Africa, 1986-1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 54)
- Soviet Union, 1986-1991 (Box JGS 18, Folder 55)
- Spain, 1986-1994 (Box JGS 18, Folder 56)
- Stamford (New York), 1993 (Box JGS 21, Folder 35)
- Stesteve (France), 1993 (Box JGS 20, Folder 32)
- Sweden, 1987-1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 57)
- Switzerland, 1986-1996 (Box JGS 18, Folder 58)
- Taiwan, 1987-1995 (Box JGS 18, Folder 59)
- Tehran, 1993-1997 (Box JGS 20, Folder 33)
- Tolentino (Italy), 1989-2003 (Box JGS 20, Folder 34)
- Trento (Italy), 1989-1996 (Box JGS 20, Folder 35)
- Tunisia, 1986 (Box JGS 18, Folder 60)
- Turkey, 1986-1996 (Box JGS 18, Folder 61)
- Uruguay, 1986-1988 (Box JGS 18, Folder 62)
- USA, 1994-1999 (Box JGS 21, Folder 36)
- Valencia, 1992 (Box JGS 21, Folder 37)
- Vercelli (Italy), 1990-1998 (Box JGS 20, Folder 36)
- Vladivostok, 1989-1990 (Box JGS 21, Folder 38)
- Waddington (England), 1988-1989 (Box JGS 20, Folder 37)
- Washington, D.C., undated (Box JGS 21, Folder 39)
- West Germany, 1982-1996 (Box JGS 18, Folder 63)
- Yomiuri (Japan), 1988-1994 (Box JGS 21, Folder 40)
- Zaporozhje (CCCP), 1991 (Box JGS 21, Folder 41)
- Zielona Gora, 1989 (Box JGS 21, Folder 42)
- Witty World Correspondence- Unsorted, 1980s-2000 (Box JGS 22)
  Scope and Contents
  Materials in this box are unprocessed.
- Correspondence; Topic files; Witty World files- Unsorted, 1980s-2000s (Box JGS 23)
  Materials in this box are unprocessed
- Correspondence- Unsorted, 1980s-2000s (Box JGS 24)
- Witty World Correspondence- Unsorted, 1980s-2000s (Box JGS 25)
- International Correspondence; Clippings- Unsorted, 1980s-2000s (Box JGS 26)